Personally...
I liked Miyamura-kun's hair long.
Miyamura!
They're making a sequel to
that horror movie you liked.
R-Really...?
He was one of the few kids in class
who wore glasses like me,
and his long hair gave him
an air of mystery.
It was great.
Watabe!
About that reference book I asked about...
Let's go see it when it hits the theater.
What? Oh, um... sure.
But this fun-loving
Miyamura-kun is nice, too.
Watabe?
Hey, Watabe, why'd you just take a picture?
To memorialize Miyamura-kun.
Memorialize him?
Watabe-kun, what're you reading?
Oh, Miyamura-kun!
Is it a mystery novel?
Yeah, it's really good.
It's got some horror elements,
but if you can get past those...
Cool.
You guys talk about horror
stuff sometimes, right?
I kind of like it, too.
Especially Japanese horror movies.
Oh, it's Hori-san who likes it.
You two would probably get along great.
Ah, I s-see...
Oh, b-but I also like it, of course!
Really? So you're into it, too, huh?
Yeah...
What is this? Why is Watabe
wearing his heart on his sleeve like this?
I can't believe we like the same stuff!
I can recommend a few more books!
Great...
Hello, everyone!
Miyamura-kun, listen to this!
I made chawanmushi today!
Let's all have some together!
Chawanmushi, huh?
Miyamura, listen to this!
It has ginko nuts in it! I put them in!
Hey, nice job!
Like father, like son.
Oh, Hori-s—
Stop!
Huh? Um...
What is this?
You stink of Watabe.
It's normally Toru or Shindo-kun...
H-H-Hold it! You're choking me!
I can't breathe!
I usually smell one of them on you.
How do you even know
what Watabe-kun smells like?
I took samples in case
something like this happened.
Something like what?
Can you really smell someone
after I just talk to them?
Girls not register. Only guys register.
Why are you talking like a robot?
I don't smell anything.
You don't need to be able to.
I can, and that's what counts.
Great dog
No, I mean...
I don't think I'd know if you'd
been with someone else.
You mean if I hung out with a series
of guys every day like you do?
I don't like the way you phrased that,
but basically, yes.
I'd never do that.
No, it's not about that.
If you hung out with Ishikawa-kun
or the student council president,
I wouldn't be able to tell like you can.
Okay, then I'll tell you.
If I cheat on you, I'll come out and say it.
Thanks, that's a big help.
Right?
Weird
Kinda weird
Dinner's ready!
And then she gets all angry...
It's not like I was any good
at studying before.
Of course, that means I need
to buckle down even harder.
Seems that way.
You've got it pretty good, Ishikawa.
If I so much as put some music on,
the cord gets pulled out.
Seriously? That's crazy.
I wish they wouldn't expect so much from us.
We're doing the best we can.
What was that about?!
I can't tell...
Probably some Hori thing or something.
Yeah, that checks out.
They're both kinda weird.
Through
and
through
You so rarely invite me over. What's up?
Not that I don't love coming.
Oh, you don't need to return that controller.
I have more at home.
That's not why I called you here.
And I'm not giving back the controller.
What's up, then?
Close...
Close your eyes.
Wait, what?
Are you gonna do something to me?
Yeah— Not really.
It'll only take a moment.
Wh-What will?
What are you gonna do in that moment?
Take my life?
You wouldn't understand, so I'm not saying.
Just hurry up and close your eyes.
What?! What are you gonna
do once I'm not looking?!
Would you keep it quiet? Just calm down!
There. Now I know what you smell like.
You're the one most likely to make a move.
On who?
H-Huh? What's this about?
Shut up.
Miyamura in Hori mode
Watabe, I honestly don't want to...
But can I ask you something
that no one else will?
Watabe.
Oh, sorry.
Hang on. I just gotta move these
to my Miyamura-kun folder.
I saw you take that picture
of Miyamura before...
Wait, your Miyamura folder?!
That's creepy.
Watabe, do you... y'know...
like Miyamura?
It goes far beyond liking him.
I can't explain it.
It's a great fascination.
Wh-What?
But Miyamura has a girlfriend.
Sorry, Ishikawa-kun.
I don't know what you're getting at.
Miyamura-kun dating the
opposite sex is just adorable.
He has guy friends at other schools, too.
Like Shindo.
So Miyamura-kun has guy friends
at other schools, eh?
So creepy!
No! I shouldn't think that about my friends!
Conflicted
So, Watabe, you're satisfied
just watching Miyamura?
I'd love to touch him if I could!
Sorry, that isn't what I meant.
Do you think you want to talk to him?
Don't worry about that! I recorded him!
Hey, Watabe-kun!
I'm getting more worried...
Hey!
Come play with us!
Watabe vision
Ishikawa-kun, even if a two-kilometer asteroid
fell on me right now, I would die happy.
He's shining so brightly.
Are you sure? An asteroid that
size would kill Miyamura, too.
You stink!
I can smell him!
It's Watabe again!
His scent is even stronger today!
He's marking you!
You're ripping it!
I don't really understand...
but you're saying
Watabe-kun got close to me?
You smell of Shindo-kun and Tanihara too,
but Watabe's scent is the strongest.
After all, Watabe has a stronger interest
in you than any of the other guys.
How does his scent tell you that much?
I didn't even touch him.
It doesn't matter if you touched him or not.
I know what you smell like, at least.
I can't really tell with
Yoshikawa-san or Ayasaki-san.
I thought you'd finally do it.
Huh?
You turned around so suddenly...
I thought you were finally going
to be rough with me!
Stop getting my hopes up!
W-Was what I did so bad
that it made you cry?!
I'm sorry!
Don't touch me!
Miyamura, you dummy!
Jealousy
No more deodorizer, please!
Were you in an accident?
Nope, a man-made disaster.
Hori, huh?
Why? Did you have another fight?
Yeah.
She really got you good.
I'm not apologizing this time,
no matter what.
Good morning.
Hori-san, what happened to your face?
That must hurt!
Dude, did you hit her back?
No way!
Miyamura, you dummy!
What is it? If you wanna
say something, out with it!
No, I don't.
You're talking dumb stuff,
so I'm going home, dummy.
Hey, who are you calling a dummy?!
You really piss me off!
She got so worked up she
smacked right into the wall.
So, what were you fighting about?
I forgot, just like always.
This time, I won't budge
until Hori-san apologizes!
How manly.
Yeah, good luck with that.
Student Council
I can't believe him!
He wasn't even the least bit bothered!
Stupid Miyamura!
Th-There, there...
Still, it's not about another girl.
Maybe it's not that big a deal?
Guys are just as dangerous.
You okay, Kyon-Kyon?
Did you hit your head?
Are you listening, Sengoku?!
Why not just apologize to him?
Why should I?!
Why should you?
What will you do if Miyamura-kun...
stops caring about you, Kyo-chan?
This could mean losing someone
who's always been there for you.
When Sengoku says it, it pisses me off,
but when Kono-san says it,
it brings me to my senses.
I... I guess you're right.
Hey.
But I'm still angry.
This is gonna take a while...
Each group has to submit their feedback.
Ignooore
I'm gonna put this together.
That okay with you?
Sure.
RUMBLE
Who cares if you answered at the same time?!
Damn, you guys are tiring me out.
Sorry to involve you.
Honestly, I'm tired, too.
Why am I so angry again?
Come on. At least remember
the reason you were fighting.
You guys need to make up quick.
I want to.
Hey, a message.
Hori-san
My period's late
Dummy
Ready to die?
Hori-san
Just kidding, dummy
Yoshikawa, I need some tissues.
Ew, Toru, you smell like apples.
What am I doing?
How stupid can I be?
I just need to say I'm sorry.
This is my fault.
Miyamura, c'mere.
Have you seen Hori?
She wasn't in class.
And she wasn't in the clinic.
Or the changing room. I'm worried.
The changing room? Did you go in there?
Well, that aside...
Did you go in?
She left her bag behind,
and it's cold outside.
Yeah.
Huh? Outside?
There she is.
What?
Nothing.
You don't care about me anymore, right?
Huh?
You might not be with me someday, right?
Uh...
You hate me, don't you?
Why would I?
B-Because I...
What? Are you crying?
Come on. There's nothing to cry about it.
But... But... I always...
get angry and treat you unfairly...
So she realizes it.
Let me see your face, Hori-san.
There!
Hey...
Wow, Hori-san's in tears.
I guess even monsters can cry.
Your nose and ears are red and everything.
She's crying, crying, crying up a river.
How embarrassing!
Shut up!
H-How can you be so nice?!
You make me worry what would
happen if you started hating me!
Wh-What? That's what you were worried about?
Hori-san, you always call me a dummy,
but you're just as much of a fool.
I know that! You really are a dummy!
Oh, so you knew.
Also, I like you a lot more
than you seem to realize.
It'd be really hard to hate you.
You always say stuff like that, dummy!
Dummymura!
It's true, though.
Okay then, I'm sorry I like you.
Damn, I apologized even though
it wasn't my fault.
That's right! You didn't do anything wrong!
It's always my fault!
Got it?
Yeah.
I dunno what they're talking about,
but Hori kicked Miyamura
in the gut, didn't she?
Yeah.
Scary.
Good morning.
Hey! Morning, Miya...mura...
A hoodie?!
What's up with that, Miyamura?
It doesn't really suit you.
That looks like a nice, warm hoodie.
Honest friends
It doesn't really suit you, though.
Thanks for that.
I've never seen you in one.
Erm, all my clothes are in the wash.
I see.
It's nice to change things up a bit.
M...
Maybe you're right.
Yep.
Morning!
Hey, someone let me borrow
their modern Japanese book!
Whoa, what's this, Miyamura?
We're both wearing hoodies!
Are you copying my style?
No, he's not.
He's not!
But we're still dressed the same!
It's cold, so I want to
tell people about hoodies,
but still no one wears them,
and I feel so defeated!
Yeah, probably because
they're against the dress code.
But you've got too many layers on.
You need to show it off.
Okay...
He's violating the dress code,
but you want him to show it off?
There!
Put those sunglasses back
in the student council room!
From that time
Miyamura, hold your fingers like this.
Yeah!
Y-Yeah?
Enough!
Take this textbook and
get back to your class!
Tch.
Why in the world is Shu so big on hoodies?
Maybe they're like his favorite equipment.
I'd have to be more like Iura before I went
around flaunting something like this.
Don't you dare try to be like Iura.
In fact, be like anyone except him.
Iura-kun...
Ah, it's true! That's against the dress code!
Oh, good morning, President.
Good morning.
I just ran into Iura-kun.
He said you'd come around on "his style."
I'm not. This is just for today.
Iura was wearing a hoodie, too.
Did you scold him?
No, not at all.
He's a lost cause.
Resigned
Iura-kun...
Let's get some lunch!
Hey, they've got a new flavor of hot tea.
Did you see it this morning?
Really? What kind?
One you'll like.
Go, go!
Wait, Miyamura.
Your hood needs fixing.
Oh, really?
Thanks.
You need to straighten
it out after you mess with it.
Wh-What was that for?!
Miyamura, that hoodie...
Let's get going!
I can't fool Hori-san...
Miyamura.
You wearin' a hoodie tomorrow, too?
No, I'll just wear my cardigan.
Stare...
Miyamura, are you coming over today?
No, I need to get home.
Did something happen between them again?
Who knows?
Good morning, Hori-san.
Good morning.
It's pretty warm today, huh?
Yeah, the sun's shining.
Aren't you cold without a scarf, though?
Stare...
Hori-san?
Come with me.
Is something wrong?
Hori-san...
It smells like you!
Here
Huh? O-Oh, yeah?
I didn't realize what she was up to.
Yeah, this is your scent.
Your hoodie smelled like someone else.
Stare...
Um...
It was Shindo's.
He left it at my place
the last time he stayed over.
That's what I figured.
How could you tell? I washed it.
It was obvious.
Not to me.
Besides, your scent is my favorite!
Make sure you give Shindo-kun's hoodie back.
Your hands are cold!
Let's go.
Huh? Oh, um, okay...
Just gonna leave it at that?
Oh, good morning!
G-Good morning!
What's going on?
Y'know...
It's a warm day.
Next time
page.11 Chocolate